Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art public programs records, circa 1995-2011 COR0003.5.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Program files, financial records, and calendar productions, 1994-2011; Series 1
  - 1/30/96 Amama, Winter FY96, 1996 January 30; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - 2/5/96 Hartke, Winter FY96, 1996 February 5; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - 2/6/96 Rose, Winter FY96, 1996 February 6; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - 2/7/96 Psycho Film, Winter FY96, 1996 February 7; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - 2/12/96 Anders, Winter FY96, 1996 February 12; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - 2/18/96 Chihuly, Winter FY96, 1996 February 18; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - 2/21/96 Narasimhan, Winter FY96, 1996 February 21; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - 2/22/96 aRT2art, Winter FY96, 1996 February 22; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - 2/27/96 Ludwig, Winter FY96, 1996 February 27; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - 2/28/96 Psycho Film, Winter FY96, 1996 February 28; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - 3/3/96 New Danish Saxophone Quartet Winter FY96, 1996 March 3; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - 3/4/96 Interact, Winter FY96, 1996 March 4; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - 3/5/96 French Films Winter FY96, 1996 March 5; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - 3/6/96 Psycho Film, Winter FY96, 1996 March 6; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - 3/13/96 Psycho Film, Winter FY96, 1996 March 13; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - 3/15/96 ADCMW, Winter FY96, 1996 March 15; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - 3/17/96 Macdonald, Winter FY96, 1996 March 17; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - 3/18/96 Hospice, Winter FY96, 1996 March 18; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - 3/20/96 Kahn Carroll, Winter FY96, 1996 March 20; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - 3/25/955 Hospice, Winter FY96, 1995 March 25; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - 3/27/95 Shakespeare Considered Winter FY96, 1996 March 27; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - 4/1/96 Hospice Winter FY96, 1996 April 1; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - 3/28/96 Pelli, Winter FY96, 1996 March 28; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Winter Gen Info. FY96 Adver., 1996; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Jan-Feb 96 Brochure Raw Materials, 1996; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Corcoran: Night Day Jan/Feb 1996, 1996 January-February; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Spec. Events for Shakespeare Lovers, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Public Programs Monthly Calendar Reports FY1996, Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Hard Materials March-April, 1996 March-April; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Corcoran: Night Day March-April 1996, 1996 March-April; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - 4/3/96 Cullen, Spring FY96, 1996 April 3; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - 4/9/96 Nicky Silver Spring FY96, 1996 April 9; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - 4/10/96 Liedtke, Spring FY96, 1996 April 10; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - 4/11/95 Argentina, Spring FY96, 1995 April 11; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - 4/16/96 What's Hot, What's Not Around Town FY96, 1996 April 16; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - 4/26/96 Lambert, Spring FY96, 1996 April 26; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - 4/28/96 Lens to Lens Spring FY96, 1996 April 28; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - 4/30/96 A Good Dying Spring FY96, 1996 April 30; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - 4/23/95 Gross, Spring FY96, 1995 April 23; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - 5/2, 5/9, 5/16, 5/23/96 Spring FY96 Great Cathedrals of France, 1996 May 2,9,16,23; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - 5/2/95 17th St Walking Tour, Spring FY96, 1995 May 2; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - 5/8/96 Environmental Film Fest Spring FY96, 1996 May 8; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Free Convo. Services Referrel System, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - So Much of our Future Depends on Preserving Our Past, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Aunt Sallie's Lament Chronical Books, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Joshua Heller Rare Books, Inc. List 21 Sprung 1995, Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Matting and Framing Works of Art on Paper pamphlets, 1994; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - DAR Library Pamphlet/Map, 1990 December; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Claire Van Vliet, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - 5/8/96 Handmade Books Spring FY96, 1995 May 8; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Lifestyle of the Rich and Famous CANCELLED, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - La Victoire Fall FY 96 Program Information, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Les Delices de la Solitude FY96 Program Information, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Les Arts et Les Sciences FY96 Programs Information, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Le Violon de Orphee Program Information FY96, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Le Violins of Lafayette FY96 General Correspondence, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - 3/17/96 Lafayette, Winter FY96, 1996 March 17; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - A Time for Justice Fall FY96 General Correspondence, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - A Time for Justice Fall FY96 Program Information, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - An Evening With Olga Hirshhorn Fall FY 96 General Correspondence, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - An Evening With Olga Hirshhorn Fall FY 96 Program Information, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - A Trip Up The Rhine Fall FY96 General Correspondence, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - A Trip Up The Rhine Fall FY 96 Program Information, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Hopper His Silent Collaboratr. Fall FY 96 Program Information, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Edward Hopper Silenced Collab. Fall FY 96 General Correspondence, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Architecture Film Fall FY 96 General Correspondence, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Schneider on Vermeer Fall FY96 General Correspondence, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Schneider on Vermeer Fall FY96 Program Information, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - 20thc. Stylemakers Fall FY96 Program Information, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - 20thc. Stylemakers Fall FY 96 General Correspondence, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Canceled Program Fall FY 95 Cabaret with Joan Stapleton, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Australia on My Mind Lecture Wine Tasting, 1995 November 29; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Australian Lecture Fall FY 96 Program Information, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Fischl on Vermeer Fall FY 96 General Correspondence, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Fischl on Vermeer Fall FY 96 Program Information, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Bragason Concert Fall FY 96 General Correspondence, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Bragason Concert Fall FY 96 Program Information, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Discovering Hamlet Fall FY 96 General Correspondence, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Discovering Hamlet Fall FY 96 Program Information, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Source Theater Fall FY 96 General Correspondence, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Source Theater Fall FY 96 Program Information, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Islamic Ethos Hall FY 96 General Correspondence, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Islamic Ethos Hall FY 96 Program Information, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Hellekant Concert Fall FY 95 Program Information, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Hellekant Concert Fall FY 95 General Correspondence, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Seseme Street Fall FY 96 General Correspondence, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Seseme Street Fall FY 96 Program Information, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Joan Nathan Fall FY 96 General Correspondence, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Joan Nathan Fall FY 96 Program Information, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Fall FY 1996 Gen Info Adver., Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Fall FY 1996 Brochure, Circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Corcoran: Night Day Sept./Oct. 1995, 1995 September-October; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Corcoran: Night Day Nov./Dec. 1995, 1995 November-December; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Loose Papers, Circa 1997; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - PP334Cp March 2 FY97 Schubert-Brahms Concert, 1997 March 2; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - PP102L March 4 FY97 Thomas Jefferson's Monticello, 1997 March 4; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - March 13 PP124L FY97 The Romanovs, 1997 March 13; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - PP127L March 17 FY97 The Golden Agge of Gardening, 1997 March 17; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - PP118L March 19 FY97 Art As Autobiography, 1997 March 19; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - PP345TP March 24 FY97 Shakespeare Theater, 1997 March 24; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - PP346TP March 31 FY97 AR Gurney, 1997 March 31; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - PP121L March 11 FY97 W.E.B. Du Bois Biography CANCELLED, 1997 March 11; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - PP128L March 20 FY97 Jacquelin Robertson CANCELLED, 1997 March 20; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Spring FY1997 Gen. Program Info, Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Spring FY1997 Advertising, Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Night Day Info. 1997, Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - PP142 April 1 FY97 Switzerland, 1997 April 1; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - April 2 PP134L FY97 Robert Rauschenberg, 1997 April 2; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - PP21b5 April 3 FY97 Embassy Rrow Walking Tour, 1997 April 3; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - PP140L April 8 FY97 Palaces of St. Petersburg, 1997 April 8; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - CMF Thursday, April 10,1997, 1997 April 10; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Fact Sheet, 1997; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - PP April 15 FY97 Environnment Film Festival, 1997 April 15; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - PP 141L April 19 FY97 Dale Chihuly at the Corcoran, 1997 April 19; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Washington Chamber Symp. Saturday April 19, 1997, 1997 April 19; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - PP138L April 22 FY97 An Evening With Hugh Hardy, 1997 April 22; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - PP130L April 28 FY97 David Driskell, 1997 April 28; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - April 30 PP131L FY97 Venturi - Brown - Diamonstein, 1997 April 30; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - PP429SA May 6 FY97 Elizabeth Murray, 1997 May 6; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - May 12 FY98 Heidelberg School of Med., 1997 May 12; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - PP428SA May 12 FY97 Treasures of Slovakia, 1997 May 12; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - PP1149 May 13 FY97 Lillian Miller, 1997 May 13; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - PP429SB May 13 FY97 Kiki Smith, 1997 May 13; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - PP428SB May 27 FY97 An Evening of Bulgarian Culture, 1997 May 27; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - June 3 PP348CP FY97 I Love a Piano, 1997 June 3; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - PP154L June 4 FY97 Does Architecture Matter?, 1997 June 4; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - PP349CP June 5 FY97 Jenny Lind, 1997 June 5; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - PP144L June 6 FY97 A Life in Jazz: Milt Hinton, 1997 June 6; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - PP325TP June 9 FY97 Signature Theatre, 1997 June 9; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - June 10 PP153L FY97 Painting tthe Octagon's History, 1997 June 10; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - PP156L June 11 FY97 Too Much Is Never Enough, 1997 June 11; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - PP155L June 26 FY97 An Ap-Peale-Ing Evening, 1997 June 26; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - June 19 PP151L FY97 ORI Soltes, 1997 June 19; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - PP139L April 29 FY97 Poets Getting Along CANCELLED, 1997 April 29; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - PP145L May 14 FY97 The Romantic Age w/ Chpoin Delacroix CANCELLED, 1997 May 14; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - May 19 PP148L FY97 "Life Death..Peale's Mus." CANCELLED, 1997 May 19; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - PP158L May 20 FY97 The Issues In Art Today CANCELLED, 1997 May 20; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - PP146L May 28 FY97 Crazy Rhythm CANCELLED, 1997 May 28; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - PP June 1 FY97 Hampden-Sydney Music Festival CANCELLED, 1997 June 1; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - PP150L June 17 FY97 Embassy of Ireland, 1997 June 17; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - CGA April 97 calendar of events, 1997 April; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - CGA June 97 calendar of events, 1997 June; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Nov 3 PP339TP FY97 Eleanor and Alice, 1997 November 3; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Nov 6 PP107L FY97 Thurlow Tibbs, 1997 November 6; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Nov 7 PP115L FY97 Julian Schnabel in Person Basquiat, 1997 November 7; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Nov 14 PP210S FY97 Blair House/ White House Tour, 1997 November 14; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Nov 17, Feb 23, April 20 PP332CPS FY97 Angeles String Quartet, 1997 February-November; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Nov 18 PP335TP FY97 Signature Theatre, 1997 November 18; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Nov 20 PP101L FY97 Ruchard Meier in Dialogue, 1997 November 20; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Nov 25 PP102L FY97 An Evening With Vincent Scully, 1997 November 25; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Nov 25 PP113L FY97 Hungarian Evening, 1997 November 25; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Dec 2 PP111L FY97 Aboarrd The Cyberclipper, 1997 December 2; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Dec 3 PP114L FY97 An Evening With Charles Gwathmey, 1997 December 3; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Dec 7 PP213S FY97 Jewelry Workshop, 1997 December 7; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Olney Theatre - Janet Solinger 1997, Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Dec 11 PP336TP FY97 Chitra Krishnamurti, 1997 December 11; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Dec 18 PP341TP FY97 Ziva's Spanish Dance Ensamble, 1997 December 18; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Contemporary Music Forum Thursday, December 19, 1996, 1996 December 19; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Sept-Oct N, 1996 September-October; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Nov-Dec N, 1996; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Sibyls in Art CANCELLED, 1997; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Advertisting, Gen. Cor. etc. 1996-97, 1996-1997; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Jan-Feb 1997 N, 1997 January-February; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - March-April 1997 N, 1997 March-April; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Jan. 14,21,28, Feb. 4 PP426S Current State of the Media FY97, 1997 January-February; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Jan. 15 PP343CP FY97 Fascinatin' Rhythm, 1997 January 15; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Jan. 22 PP116L FY97 Framing Right or Wrong, 1997 Janaury 22; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Jan. 27 PP117L FY97 Edith Wharton: A House Full..., 19977 January 27; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Jan. 29 PP122L FY97 James Wines: Green Architecture, 1997 Jauary 29; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - PP347CP February 5 FY97 Life Upon The Wicked Stage, 1997 February 5; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Washington Chamber Symp. Saturday, February 8, 1997, 1997 February 8; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Feb. 11, 18, 25, Mar. 18, 23 PP427S Nights of Opera FY97, 1997 February-March; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - PP338CPA Feb. 12, Mar. 26, Apr. 9 FY97 Kamermuziek, 1997 February-April; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Contemporary Music Forum Thursday, February 13, 1997, 1997 February 13; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - PP214S February 15 FY97 Dior The Renaissance of French Fash., 1997 February 15; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Feb. 18 PP137L FY97 Pre-Raphaelite Victorian Art, 1997 February 18; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Feb. 19 PP119L FY97 Stanley Tigerman, 1997 February 19; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - PP126L February 24 FY97 This Little Light of Mine: Banneker, 1997 Febrruaryy 24; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - PP125L February 26 FY97 An Evening With James Rosenquist, 1997 February 26; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - PP123L February 27 FY97 Martisor Day Celebration, 1997 February 27; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - CMF, 1996-1997; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - WCS Series, 1996-1997; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - 1997 Calendars, Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Monthly Event Calendars, 1996; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Advertising, Circa 1996; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Presidency: Prelude to Campaign 1996, 1996 July; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Kafka, Beer, Playwrights Other..., 1997 July 10; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Cabaret: The Symingtons in Song, 1997 July 15; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - The New Wave: Before, During and After, 1997 July - 1997 August; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - A Vicarious Journey... Central Italy and Sicily, 1997 July 24; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Tradition Chinese Culutre in Taiwan, 1997 July 31; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - [Loose Promotional Material], Circa 1996; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Homage to George Burns, 1997 August 1; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - An Architectural Paradigm for the Nation's Capital, 1997 August 7; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Blues in the Night, 1997 September 12; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Portuguese Style: 4 Centuries, 4..., 1997 September 16; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Direct from the Middle East, 1997 September 18; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Insider's Embassy Row Tour, 1997 September 26; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Night Day, 1996-1997; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Jan Steen: Wit of Holland's... Cancelled, 1997 July 11; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - The Unabomber Cancelled, 1997 August 6; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Homage to Philip Johnson, 1997 September 25; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence/Advertising Fall 1997, Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Capital Tales, 1997 October 2; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Guillermo Gomez-Pena, 1997 October 6; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - The Violins of Lafayette, 1997; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Our Lives ata the Met, 1997 October 7; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - We Have a Song to Sing, O, 1997 October 8; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Nights of Opera, 1997; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Danish Tivoli Performance, 1997 October 11; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Fabulous Finnish Faberge, 1997 October 1997; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Italian Fashion, 1997 October 19; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Kieslowski Film Series, 1997; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - An Evening With Robert Stern, 1997 October 29; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Washington Chamber Symphony, 1997-1998; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Contemporary Music Forum, 1997-1998; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - 1st Quarter Summer Advertising, 1998; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - 1st Quarter Summer General Correspondence, 1998; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Night and Day 1997, 1997 July - 1997 August; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Night and Day 1998, 1998 September - 1998 October; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Music of the People/Cohen, 1998 July 1; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Picasso: The Early Years, 1998 July 1; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Altair Trio, 1998 July; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - An Evening in Exotic Thailand, 1998 July 10; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - The Line King, 1998 July 17; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Cesar Pelli/National Airport, 1998 July 24; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Cartier: Art of Adornment, 1998 July 28; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - The Victorians, 1998 July 29; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Tony Gil/Very Thought of You, 1998 July 30; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Wyeth/A Secret Life, 1998 August 5; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - That's Jazz, 1998 August 11; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Memorialization of the Mall, 1998 August 14; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Evening of Magical Storytelling, 1998 August 14; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Hungary/A Musical Tribute, 1998 September 11; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Angeles String Quartet, 1998 September 14; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Villa I Tatti, 1998 September 17; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Violins of Lafayette, 1998; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Frank Gehry, 1998 September 23; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Women in Theatre, 1998 September 22; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Woolly Mammoth/Brian Freeman, 1998 September 23; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - American Fashion Today, 1998 September 27; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Sexuality in Art, 1998 September 29; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Robert Graham Buildings Cancelled, 1998 October 21; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Tancredi Evening of Music Cancelled, 1998 August 4; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - 2nd Quarter Fall Advertising, 1998; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - 2nd Quarter Fall General Correspondence, 1998; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Inside Capital Hill Walking Tour, 1998 October 9; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Crossing Over/Changing Places, 1998; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Spanish Dance Society, 1996; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Blair House/White House Tour, 1998 October 16; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - David Levinthal, 1998 October 20; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Gordon Parks, 1998 October 23; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Time-Warner Collaboration Half Past Autumn: The Art of Gordon Parks, Circa 1998; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - The Drama League - Not Official Program, 1998 October 25; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Betrayal Film Series, 1998; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - P. Fay Series, 1998; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Woolly Mamoth/Dennis Potter, 1998 November 3; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Versailles, 1998 November 8; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Julie Taymore, 1998 November 17; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Architectural Design Series, 1998 November- 1998 December; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Ronal Reagan Building Tour, 1998 December 2; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Ellerbe Becket, Circa 1998; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Philadelphia Musuem of Art Tour, 1998 December 6; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - I Love a Piano II, 1998 December 8; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Night and Day 1997, 1997 November - 1997 December; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Corcoran 100th Birthday Celebration Cancelled, 1998 October 5; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Walter Persegati Cancelled, 1998 October 14; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Political Series Cancelled, 1998 October - 1998 November; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Feminism COntemporary Art, 1998 December 8; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Georgetown Walking Tour Cancelled, 1998 November 4; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Lillian Bassman Cancelled, 1998 November 20; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Seven Guitars Cancelled, 1998 December 11; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Ikebana Demonstration Cancelled, 1998 December 13; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - 3rd Quarter WInter Advertising and General Correspondence, 1998; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - CGA Night Day 1998, 1998 January - 1998 February; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - CGA Calendar, 1998 March; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Arcchitecture Series, 1998 January - 1998 February; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Treasures of the Russian North, 1998 January 21; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Rusty Hassan, 1998 January 22; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Peter Robinson Concert, 1998 January 26; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Embassy of Turkey, 1998 January 29; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - The Altair Trio, 1998; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Illustrators Series, 1998; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Studio Theatre, 1998 February 3; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 28)